Guide to the Radio TV Services Records, circa 1937-2012 UA.27.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Film and Video, circa 1937-1987 and undated
  - Film, 1936-1979
    - China reel 2, 1970s
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 39, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0245)
    - Football, 1971-09-30
      The date above is written on the film's leader; however, Duke did not play a game on Sept. 30, 1971. Possibly this film is of Duke's Sept. 25 game against Virginia, or of Duke's Oct. 30 game against Georgia Tech.
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 20, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0214)
    - Selected highlights of the Epoch Campaign announcement. Speakers included Sanford, Jones, McMahon, 1973-09-27; 16mm, color, sound; 0:09:52
      1 film reel: 7 inch.; There is a xeroxed script for the Epoch Campaign entitled For Humankind and History: A Time for Greatness at Duke in folder 5, box 3.; Numbered: D-8; Duplication Master: Beta SP. UA88-57-9; Highlights of the Epoch Campaign Announcement appear on Duplication Master: Beta SP. UA88-57-12; Highlights of the Epoch Campaign Announcement appear on Reference Copy: VHS. UA88-57-12
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 15, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0063)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0042, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0063.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0042, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0063.mp4)
    - Epoch Campaign Announcement: T. Sanford, J. A. Jones, Alex McMahon, 1973-09-27; 16mm, color, silent; 0:02:02
      Duplication Master: Beta SP. UA88-57-10
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 5, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0215)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0120, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0215.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0120, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0215.mp4)
    - Card Tricks, 1973 circa; 16mm, color, silent; 0:01:03
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 6, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0225)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0130, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0225.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0130, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0225.mp4)
    - Football, 1973 circa; 16mm, color, silent; 0:00:40
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 6, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0227)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0132, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0227.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0132, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0227.mp4)
    - Good campus (color), students studying, 1973 circa; 16mm, color, silent; 0:00:57
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 6, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0230)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0135, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0230.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0135, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0230.mp4)
    - A Time for Greatness at Duke, 1974; 16mm, color, sound;
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 15, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0073)
    - U.S.S. Monitor Discovery, 1974-03-07
      1 film reel: sd.; 7 inch.; Note on can: Orig. Magnetic Sound. Original film of news conference held to announce the finding of the U.S.S. Monitor by Duke Univ. and other researchers.; Numbered: C-163; Duplication Master: Beta SP. UA88-57-3
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 14, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0056)
    - The Luxury of Doing Good, 1974-04-17; 16mm, color, sound; 0:09:55
      1 film reel: 7 inch.; Duplication Master: Beta SP. UA88-57-8
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 15, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0070)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0045, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0070.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0045, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0070.mp4)
    - Removing Fossils & Rock, 1975; 16mm, color, sound; 0:02:44
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 6, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0218)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0123, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0218.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0123, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0218.mp4)
    - Duke, WRAL-TV, 1975-01-22
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 38, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0243)
    - 50th Anniversary Convocation Processional with Duke statue & pickets, 1975-04-12; 16mm, color, silent; 0:03:01
      Duplication Master: Beta SP. UA88-57-11; Highlights of the 50th Anniversary Convocation Processional appear on Duplication Master: Beta SP. UA88-57-12; Highlights of the 50th Anniversary Convocation Processional appear on Reference Copy: VHS. UA88-57-12
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 5, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0216)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0121, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0216.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0121, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0216.mp4)
    - 50th Anniversary Graduation, 1975-05; 16mm, color, silent; 0:03:05
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 6, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0217)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0122, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0217.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0122, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0217.mp4)
    - Egg Drop, 1979-11-13; 16mm, color, silent; 0:03:09
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 6, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0219)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0124, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0219.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0124, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0219.mp4)
    - Tipton, undated
      1 film reel: black and white; 5 inch.
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 15, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0117)
    - untitled, undated
      1 film reel: col.; 3 inch.; From Description of Films: Two The Ends; Alumni House; Someone walking across campus; Numbered: 8
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 16, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0078)
    - Basketball, undated
      1 film reel: col.; 3 inch.; From Description of Films: Duke team #'s 10 and 31; Playing a team wearing white uniforms with red letters; Duke player (20); (10) is a forward (20) is a guard (33) maybe center; Numbered: 11
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 37, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0080)
    - Football Clips, undated
      1 film reel: b&w; 3 inch.; From Description of Films: Scene looking from top of Chapel down campus drive; Bill Murray talks to football player (60); Football practice in background; Photograph of Football squad; Photos of individual players: #'s 83, 71, 63; Players getting down over the ball center (58); #'s 60, 74, 80 all lined up being introduced & charge down the field; Orange Bowl Classic 1957 Miami, Florida; Duke vs. Nebraska; Parade down field for Orange Bowl; Football plays from that game; Crowd shot at end; Numbered: 13
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 16, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0082)
    - Football, undated; 16mm, black-and-white, silent; 0:01:48
      1 film reel: b&w; 3 inch.; From Description of Films: Coach Bill Murray & players on field; Players numbers we can see: 18, 46, 33, 35; 20-going to kick ball; 18-pass the ball; 37-fullback/halfback; 46-carrying ball; 35-carrying ball; 41-carrying ball and passing; Entire squad running through a practice scrimmage play-48 receives; Parade down field; Football plays Duke vs. ? (some kind of bowl game) was a touchdown made; Duke vs. Nebraska in Orange Bowl. Score on board Duke 7 - Nebraska 0 (nearly 12 minutes to go when this picture was taken; Numbered: 14
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 16, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0083)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0007, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0083.mov)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0007, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0083.mp4)
    - Untitled, undated
      1 film reel: col.; 3 inch.; From Description of Films: (full of tape splices); Group of men sitting around table, individual close-up of two men, then group shot of the men again; Overlooking (possibly) the hospital parking lot; Into the hospital; Two people in white coats working with a patient; Close-up of computer machine; Band performing on field; Card section at Duke Stadium-face of pirate; Brief crowd shot; Somebody lecturing (very dark); Some people (you tried to identify some Charles Wade and Clarence Whitefield); Arthur Larson talking on the phone; Looking through the gardens (long); Golf course and putting green; People at edge of swimming pool (out of focus); Air ROTC marching pass briefly; Rifle inspection; Numbered: 16
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 16, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0085)
    - Duke vs. Tennessee (football), undated
      1 film reel: b&w; 3 inch.; From Description of Films: original footage (tape edits in it); Program of game; Looking down from top of chapel at the city; Panning across top of buildings; Numbered: 20
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 16, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0088)
    - Titles: Duke Army Game, undated
      1 film reel: b&w; 3 inch.; Numbered: 25
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 16, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0092)
    - untitled, undated
      1 film reel: col.; 7 inch.; From Description of Films: From Description of Films: Ernie Greup talking to two men on sofa; Sign on wall behind men Here is your Hoof'n'Horn Show Laughing With You; Float people dressed in Scottish uniforms/some kind of parade; Piano and band being unloaded; Bunch of people in front of building on east; Girls in dressing room fixing hair; Band performing Les Brown and his Band of Renown graduate of Duke; People dancing; Trumpet player; Two people walking away from chapel; Girls doing can-can; Numbered: 29
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 15, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0095)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina, undated
      1 film reel: b&w; 7 inch.; From Description of Films: about 300 ft; Old Duke Stadium; Band marching up field; Bill Murray talking with another coach; (21) kick on catch ball; (27) passing the ball; Football plays start; (17) quarterback takes the ball hands back to fullback left-handed pass down field; (47) running ball makes fine gain; (27) takes ball and scores; Shot of crowd; (17) passes ball to (8) who goes out of bounds; (17) bulldogs around side; Scoreboard Duke 13 Visitors 7; Touchdown and recovers fumble; Another touchdown; On 8 yard line; 4th quarter 3 1/2 minutes to go score Duke 13, Visitors 21; Numbered: 30
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 15, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0096)
    - Duke-Army Football Highlights, Composite Sound Print #II, undated
      1 film reel: sd., b&w; 7 inch.; From Description of Films: Same as reel 32; Numbered: 33
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 16, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0099)
    - Duke vs. Army Football Highlights Neg Track, undated
      1 film on core, no reel, in 7-inch can.
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 16, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0109)
    - Football: Purdue Rally Deadlocks Duke, undated
      1 film reel: sd., b&w; 3 inch.
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 16, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0111)
    - Unknown, undated
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 19, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0135)
    - Unknown, undated
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 20, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0236)
    - Unknown, undated
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 20, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0237)
    - Unknown, undated
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 20, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0238)
    - Duke Gardens Orig. 100' Production, undated
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 20, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0239)
  - Video, 1981-1987, undated (Box 21)
    Subjects include the U.S.S. Monitor, lemurs, the proposed Nixon library at Duke, Terry Sanford, and an Easter service at the chapel.
    Arrangement note
    Arranged alphabetically by title.
    - Aquanautics Corporation: The Artificial Gill, undated, 1 videocassette (U-matic; 21:00). (Box 21)
    - Bamboo Lemurs, 1987, 1 videocassette (U-matic; approx. 10:00). (Box 21)
    - Duke University 1982-1983 ACC School, Profile & Footage used to produce that Profile for Raycom / Jefferson Productions Sports Network, Apr. 16, 1983, 1 videocassette (U-matic). (Box 21)
    - Duke University Chapel Easter Worship Service, Apr. 11, 1982, 1 videocassette (U-matic). (Box 21)
    - Monitor Search Seq., undated, 1 video reel (2:29): 6 1/2-inch reel, 2 inch tape. (Box 21)
    - NBC Nightly News: Nixon Library, Aug. 27, 1981, 1 videocassette (U-matic). (Box 21)
    - NBC Nightly News: Nixon Library Controversy, Aug. 27, 1981, 1 videocassette (U-matic; 2:12). (Box 21)
    - New Duke Scholarships and Grants, undated, 1 videocassette (U-matic; 1:59). (Box 21)
    - 60 Minutes: Terry Sanford, Jan. 25, 1981, 1 videocassette (U-matic; 52:00). (Box 21)
    - Student Life in the United States, Apr. 20, 1981, 1 videocassette (U-matic; 29:05). (Box 21)
- Accessions UA88-57, UA91-53, UA2008-0048, UA2008-0065, UA2012-0041, 6
  Accession contains video tape (mostly VHS, 2 DVDs, some BetaMax) of events related to Duke occurring both on and off campus. Some topics include NC People (Nan Keohane, Keith Brodie, Richard Brodhead, Terry Sanford); history of Duke stone; Duke Primate Center; Graduate 1997; NCAA championship bonfire; convocations, baccalaureate services, graduations, tributes (John Burness, Jerry Black). Noted speakers include Pres. Brodhead, Pres. Keohane, John Hope Frankin, Cokie Roberts, Janet Reno, George Bush, etc.
  Electronic records in this series have been migrated to a library server and digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library Reading Room. To request access, please contact Research Services before coming to use these records.
  - Duke Memorial, (Master Broadcast), 1996-09-30; 3/4-inch (Box 21, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Umatic-0001)
  - The Artificial Gll: Aquanautrics Corporaion, undated; 3/4-inch (Box 21, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Umatic-0002)
  - 60 Minutes, Terry Sanford, 1981, 1981-01-25; 3/4-inch (Box 21, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Umatic-0003)
  - NBC Nightly News, Nixon Library Controversy, Dave Riggs, Producer, 1981-08-27; 3/4-inch (Box 21, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Umatic-0004)
  - New Duke Scholarships and Grants, undated; 3/4-inch (Box 21, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Umatic-0005)
  - Duke University, 1982-1983, Profile and Footage used to produce "That Profile for Raycom/ Jefferson Productions Sports Network, 1983-04-06; 3/4-inch (Box 21, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Umatic-0006)
  - Bamboo Lemurs found in Madagascar, 1987-07-13; 3/4-inch (Box 21, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Umatic-0007)
  - Duke University Chapel Easter Worship Service, 1982-04-11; 3/4-inch (Box 21, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Umatic-0008)
  - Student Life in the United States, 1981-04-20; 3/4-inch (Box 21, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Umatic-0009)
  - Kimberly Aiken, 1994; 3/4-inch (Box 21, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Umatic-0010)
  - Orrin Pilkey, Beachfront Development/Erosion, undated; 3/4-inch (Box 21, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Umatic-0011)
  - Nixon Library Cutspot, 1981-08-27; 3/4-inch (Box 21, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Umatic-0012)
  - Duke University Campus B-Roll 2007 Reel (Latest), Betacam (Box 22, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Bcam-0001)
  - Terry Sanford Inauguration Reel 1 (D-2), undated; Betacam (Box 22, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Bcam-0002)
  - Terry Sanford Inauguration Reel 2 (D-2), undated; Betacam (Box 22, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Bcam-0003)
  - This is Duke, 1954; Betacam (Box 22, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Bcam-0004)
  - Alumni Affairs, "Quest without End", 1957; Betacam (Box 22, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Bcam-0005)
  - Terry Sanford Epoch Campaign Announcement highlights, 1973 Sept. 27; Betacam (Box 22, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Bcam-0006)
  - Terry Sanford Convocation procession demonstration, 1975 April 12; Betacam (Box 22, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Bcam-0007)
  - Terry Sanford Highlights, 1969; 1973; 1975; Betacam (Box 22, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Bcam-0008)
  - Terrry Sanford Epoch Campaign news conference, 1973 Sept. 27; Betacam (Box 22, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Bcam-0009)
  - Terry Sanford Epoch Campaign: The luxury of doing good, 1974 April 17; Betacam (Box 22, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Bcam-0010)
  - Terry Sanford news conference after being named Duke's president, 1969 Dec. 14; Betacam (Box 22, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Bcam-0011)
  - News conference: Discovery of USS Monitor, 1974 Mar. 7; Betacam (Box 22, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Bcam-0012)
  - News conference: Discovery of USS Monitor, 1974 Mar. 7; Betacam (Box 22, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Bcam-0013)
  - "Loggerhead Turtle Release" -- Professor Larry Crowder, Duke University Marine Lab, 2002-12; Betacam (Box 22, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Bcam-0014)
  - Sheila Patek, Duke University Graduate Student, "Lobster Sound" Release, 2001-05-09; Betacam (Box 22, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Bcam-0015)
  - Nicholas Family Gift Announcement to Duke University, undated; Betacam (Box 22, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Bcam-0016)
  - NC People, President Nannerl O. Keohane, 2004-02-06; Betacam (Box 22)
  - LSRC B-Roll, undated; Betacam (Box 22, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Bcam-0017)
  - Campus Information Presentation, 1992-1993; Betacam-SP (Box 22, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Bcam-0019)
  - Elizabeth Dole Graduation Speech, 2000-05-14; Betacam-SP (Box 22, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Bcam-0020)
  - Diademed Sifaka (lemurs) indoors, 1995-1996; Betacam-SP (Box 22, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Bcam-0021)
  - Duke Graduation, Jimmy Carter, 1997-05-18; Betacam-SP (Box 22, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Bcam-0022)
  - "Lost City" Dive, Monte Basgall, 2000; Betacam-SP (Box 22, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Bcam-0023)
  - Basketball Celebration/Bonfire at Duke University, 1992-04-06; Betacam-SP (Box 22, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Bcam-0024)
  - 60 Minutes, Vol. XXXIV, No. 28, "A New Lease on Life", 2002-04-07; Betacam (Box 22, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Bcam-0025)
  - Duke University Stock B-Roll, 1991-08-20; Betacam-SP (Box 22, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Bcam-0026, Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0001, Video-file UA27020001-Bcam-0026.mov)
  - Romeo and Juliet (Lemurs) -- Duke University News Services, 1999-11-03; Betacam (Box 22, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Bcam-0027)
  - Duke Graduation - Cokie Roberts - 5/16/99, 1999-05-16; Betacam (Box 22, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Bcam-0028)
  - Ford Foundation Campus Diversity Q, 1998-10; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0001)
  - "Good Morning America" Duke Univ. News Service, 2002-04-29; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0002)
  - Community Economic Development Law Clinic 2002, VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0003)
  - A Story in Stone Spring 2002 TRT 4:50, 2002 Spring; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0004)
  - "College is Possible" :30 1999-2000 Halftime Spot Duke Univ. News Service, VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0005)
  - "Ties that Bind" Duke, Durham, and Martin Luther King's Legacy of Hope MLK Planning Committee, 2002 January; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0006)
  - Duke News Students - New Orleans, 2005-09-07; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0007)
  - DILR: A Third Place Celebrating 25 Years with the Duke Institute for Learning in Retirement, 2002; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0008)
  - The Duke Endowment Who is My Neighborhood? The Duke-Durham Neighborhood Partnership TRT 15:39, 2002; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0009)
  - WTVD-TV 12/7/95 Nicholas [illegible], 1995-12-07; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0010)
  - NOK Live [illegible] NBC-17, 1998-07-15; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0011)
  - Al Rossiter Retirement 10/01 Duke Univ. News Service, 2001-10; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0012)
  - "Duke University" Charlie Rose PBS National 12:47, 2003-10-16; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0013)
  - LSRC "A Building Without Walls" (VNR), undated; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0014)
  - "John Hope Franklin" Charlie Rose PBS National 01:00, 2005-12-01; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0015)
  - "Blacks Seize Allen Building", VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0016)
  - Centennial Year, 1939-1939, VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0017)
  - Doris Duke 9/30/1996, 1996-09-30; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0018)
  - North Carolina Now - 2/6/97 - Sen. Sanford, 1997-02-06; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0019)
  - Dawson's Creek #502 "The Lost Weekend", 2001; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0021)
  - Fox News Live, Fox News Channel, National, 1/24/2003, 02:02, 2003-01-24; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0022)
  - To Engineer is Human - Henry Petroski Dept. of Civil Engineering, Duke University, 50 minutes, 1987; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0023)
  - Duke: A Special Place, 1986; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0024)
  - Duke Divinity School: A School of the Church, A School of the University, undated; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0025)
  - The Divinity School, Duke University, Sharing a Vision, Program Length 11:00, undated; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0026)
  - 60 Minutes, "Queer Studies," 3/22/98, 1998-03-22; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0027)
  - Inauguration of President Keohane VNR, 10-23-1993, 1993-10-23; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0028)
  - 60 Minutes, Duke Brain Tumor Center (VHS, April 7, 2002); Approximately 30 minutes, 2002-04-07; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0029)
  - News Master, 2002-10; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0030)
  - Shroud of Turin -- New Findings by Dr. Alan and Mary Whanger; News Brief, 0:00-1:15; Presentation, 3:22-23:45; Interview, 24:03, 52:27, undated; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0031)
  - Good Morning America, 2002-04-29; VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0032)
  - Duke Tennis Study; Dr. Alex Roland - NASA, undated; VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0034)
  - ACC Halftime Spots, 2004; VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0035)
  - Wal-Mart "2000 Summer Apparel" and "2000 Spring Apparel", 2000-05-26; VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0036)
  - Robot Games, Duke University News, two segments, 1:19 and 2:36, undated; VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0037)
  - The Beaches Are Moving hosted by professor of geology Dr. Orrin H. Pilkey, Jr, undated; VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0038)
  - Inauguration of President Keohane, 1993-10-23; VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0039)
  - The Charlie Rose Show, Interview with President Nannerl O. Keohane, 1993-10-14; VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0040)
  - Good Morning America, Tim Johnson on medical innovations at Duke, 2002-04-29; VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0041)
  - Center for Documentary Studies: "Behind the Veil": WTVD broadcast, 1993-07; VHS; 0:11:52 (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0042, Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0016, Video-file UA27020001-VHS-0042.mov)